m-downloader.com 2017-06-10

# Privacy Policy - General World

We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of the personal and other information we receive from users of the GW Service. For additional data on collection and protection of your information in regards to the GW software “General Downloader”, please check the separate EULA for GW Software

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. By continuing to use the GW Services you agree with the latest available version. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service.

The purpose of the GW Services is to provide its users with an infrastructure which enables the users to search files in various file sharing and uploading sites like Mediafire.com, Uploading.com, Turbobit.net etc. The GW links its users with the file-sharing and torrent networks. None of the torrent files, peers or content is controlled by the GW administrators or servers. The same applies to the third party file hosting services. None of the files stored remotely, nor the users who have uploaded them are controlled by the GW. You agree to provide us certain information, which we collect in order to allow you to benefit from the GW Services. 

## The GW Services and third party websites

This Privacy Policy applies solely to the GW Services. The Service may contain links to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by the GW. The GW has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party website. You agree that you are responsible for reviewing and understanding the privacy policies (if any) of any third party websites you may access through this Service. By using this Service, you release the GW from any and all liability arising from your use of any third party site to which this Service may be linked.

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve the Service, to administer your subscription and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Service. Below are the types and categories of information that we collect.

## Personal Information Collected

We collect your personal information in the following ways:

## User Account

In order use the Service you do not have to create an account on any of our websites. But in order to access all features of the GW Service you will have to create a GW account. In this respect you are required to provide the following contact information, which you recognize and expressly acknowledge is personal information allowing others, including GW, to identify you: email address, username and a password chosen by you. It is important that you must keep your GW account password secure and confidential.

## Server Log Data

When you use the Service, whether as a GW subscriber or a non-registered user, the GW automatically records information about your use of the Service ("server log data"). The server log data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type, what software you were using, the web page you were visiting immediately prior to visiting our website, pages of our website that you visited, the time spent on those pages, information you searched for on our website, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze the use of the Service and for the website's technical administration, to improve the functionality and user-friendliness of the Service, and to better tailor it to our visitors' needs. We also use this information to verify that users of the Service meet the criteria required to process their requests.

## Cookies

Like most websites, the GW websites use cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows the GW to recognize you as a user when you return to the GW website using the same computer and web browser. If your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to fully use the GW websites. Like the information you enter during registration, the cookies are used to customize your experience on our website.

One type of cookies, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you have logged into your GW account. When you visit the GW website next time, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing user so you will not need to log in before using the Service. If you log out of the GW website you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log into your account.

Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the GW website. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.

We use cookies to improve the quality of our Service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. In the course of serving advertisements or optimizing the Service for our users, we may allow authorized third parties to place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. No information provided to third parties through such cookies will be personally identifiable. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can configure your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies or you opt to refuse all cookies, you may not be able to use the GW websites or Service as a whole. The GW does not store any personally identifiable information in the cookies.

## Web Beacons

We allow other companies, called ad networks, to serve advertisements to our users. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms.

To deliver these ads properly, the GW may include a file, called a web beacon, from these ad networks within pages served by the GW servers so the networks may provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers as well as to target ads to you while you visit other sites.

Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the servers of an ad network, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page directly from their site.

These general targets may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads on other sites as a substitute for random, irrelevant ads. The GW does not provide personally identifiable information to any advertiser or any other third party.

## Log files, IP addresses and information about your computer

Due to the very nature of the Internet, when you visit a GW website we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave the GW website. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), the data about your computer operating system and the type of your web browser, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the GW Service. The linkage between your IP address and your other information is not shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

## The GW Communications

The GW will communicate with you through your provided email or by notices posted on the GW websites, or through other means available through the Service, which may include text and other forms of messaging. The GW may use your email address without further consent for notifying you of major GW changes or for customer service purposes. You can change your e-mail and contact preferences at any time in your account. By registering a user account, you also agree that the GW may send commercial or marketing messages to your email.

## Sharing Information with Third Parties

The GW takes the privacy of users very seriously. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. We, however, may provide aggregated anonymous data about the usage of our Services to third parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate, including to prospective advertisers on the GW.

The GW allows other companies to place advertisements on our websites. These companies use technology to deliver advertisements you see in the Service directly to your browser. In doing so, they may automatically receive your IP address. Other companies that place advertising in the Service may have the ability to use cookies and/or web beacons to collect information, including information about your usage of the Service. We do not control the processes that advertisers use to collect information. However, IP addresses, cookies and web beacons alone generally cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines. Therefore, advertisers and others whose advertisements or content may appear in the Service generally will not know who you are unless you provide additional information to them, by responding to an advertisement, by entering into an agreement with them, or by some other means.

## Legal Disclaimer

The GW cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of the GW or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical.

## Disclosures to others

We may also disclose your personal and other information you provide, to another third party as part of reorganization or sale of the assets of the GW division or company. Any third party to which we transfer or sell GW’s assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us.

## Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to the GW. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

## Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information

We may share aggregated information that does not include personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and the server log data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your personal Information.

## International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to "and maintained on" computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to such transfer.

## Links to Other Sites

Our websites contain links to other web sites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party's web site. The fact that we link to a web site or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party web sites. These other web sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other web sites you visit.

## Accessing and Changing your Account Information

You can review the information you provided to us and make any desired changes to them, or to the settings for your GW account including your email at any time by logging into your account on a GW website. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, the GW may, for a time, retain residual information about you in its backup and/or archival copies of its database. 

## Deleting your Account

In case you wish to delete your account in the GW, you can still use the GW Service, but in limited volume, comparing to the registered users. If you delete your GW account, we may retain certain data contributed by you if we believe it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally identifiable data, account recovery or if required by law. In order to delete your account please email our support.

## Your Obligations

## As a user, you have certain obligations imposed by applicable law and regulations:

  1. You must, at all times, respect the last available version of this Privacy Policy and of the Terms of Service. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights which may belong to third parties.
  2. You must not share or otherwise disseminate any information which may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic.

Any violation of these guidelines may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your account by the GW.
